[Music]
family is everything securing your fam's
tomorrow and ensuring your peace of mind
is always our top
priority sometimes life gets busy and
essential details might slip your mind
as your trusted Insurance partner we are
here to guide you through the process of
claiming any money that may be payable
to you but lying with us as an unclaimed
amount let's understand why money moves
to unclaimed funds
[Music]
sometimes contact details change and we
are unable to reach you for any payment
due to you in such cases your money will
move to the unclaimed fund always keep
your contact details like mobile number
email ID and address updated with us
make sure your latest Bank Account
Details are updated with us for smooth
processing of payments when you're
nominated is not aware of the policies
you've taken it can lead to challenges
in reaching them always keep your
nominee informed about your insurance
policies and keep your nominee details
updated with us for our NRI customers
providing complete NRE premium payment
proof that is the bank statements with
details of all the premiums paid is
crucial for processing payment to NRE
accounts in case of pension policy
policies choosing the annuity option
post
maturity if you don't do so the money
will move to unclaimed funds after 12
months but be assured your money is
always safe with us after 10 years the
unclaimed amount moves to the senior
citizen welfare fund
scwf it stays there for 25 years and can
be claimed anytime now if you want to
check if you have any unclaimed amount
we have made it convenient for you visit
our website at
www.life.com click on the customer
services Tab and go to the unclaimed
amount section enter the required
details like policy and pan number and
click submit a message on your screen
will guide you through the following
steps to claim your funny check the
details on our mobile app go to the
service section and select payout
unclaimed
amount you can also visit our nearest
Branch with your policy details kyc and
bank account information our customer
service representative will assist you
alternatively write to us at
Lifeline iprof life.com or call our
customer care number at
[Music]
18260 from your registered mobile number
we encourage you to always stay
connected to your policy and inform us
about any changes in your contact
details bank account details and nominee
details act today and connect with us
we're here caring for you at every step
[Music]